

Contact Details

+8801712897008



avoy2008@gmail.com



House-12, Lane-8, Block-C, Pallabi, Sec-12, Mirpur, Dhaka.



Linked in

Career Summary

A pragmatic & business focused marketing professional having proven experience in diversified Pharmaceutical Brand Management, Hospital Business Development, Sales, Customer Relationship Management, Sales Force Effectiveness, Training and development etc. can work faster than average people with maximum accuracy.

Core Skills



- x Brand Activation
- Marketing Communication
- 🜟 Business Analysis
- roduct Launch
- 対 Market Research
- ★ Sales Force Excellence
- ጵ Regulatory Affairs

MD KAWSER HOSSAIN

Pharmaceutical & Healthcare Marketing Professional

8.5 Year's Experience

EXPERIENCE

Product Manager

Nov 2016 to Present

Julphar Bangladesh, a subsidiary of Julphar UAE.

- Mentored 4 Sr./Product Executives for achieving Top line & Bottom line.
- Flourishingly launched MEBO, flagship brand of Julphar UAE and secured 130% revenue in launching year.
- Revamped company website and created social media page which expedited direct customer integration
- Conserved 30% promotional cost by arranging online educational event.

Senior Product Executive

Feb 2015 to Nov 2016

Concord Pharmaceuticals Ltd.

Successfully launched Dapazin (Dapagliflozin) first time in Bangladesh Pharma market which created huge vibration.

Product Executive

May 2013 to Feb 2015

Apex Pharma Ltd.

Delivered the highest growth of Angical-50 in the year 2013.

Pharmacist

May 2011 to Jan 2013

Apollo Hospitals Dhaka

- Pioneered the Ward Pharmacist in every ward of the hospital.
- Introduced the Home Delivery Medicine service for pharmacy.
- Initiated the Mobile Pharmacy Concept in different corner of the hospital.

EDUCATION

2018	Executive Master of Business Administration (Marketing)
	American International University-Bangladesh
2015	Master of Pharmacy in Clinical Pharmacy & Molecular Pharmacology
	East West University
2011	Bachelor of Pharmacy
	East West University
2006	H.S.C
	Dhaka City College
2004	S.S.C
	Monipur High School

Mega Projects

- Launching of Dapazin
- Launching of MEBO
- Annual Conference 2018 of Julphar Bangladesh

Professional Certification

- Registered Pharmacist by Pharmacy Council of Bangladesh. Registration number: A-4512
- Certified Digital Marketer

Languages

IELTS score: 7.5 (Overall Band)

Computer Skills

MS Office

Email & Internet

SPSS

Photoshop

Personal Information

Father : Md Amzad Hossain

Mother : Shahida Amzad

Date of Birth : 14-04-1989

Nationality : Bangladeshi

References

References would be provided on request.

TRAINING

- Digital Marketing Competency
- How a salesman can become even more successful
- International Trade: Import-Export through L/C & without opening of L/C
- Cytotoxic Admixture Training
- Cardio Pulmonary Resuscitation (CPR)
- Medication management & Use
- Fire safety & Management

PROVEN JOB ROLES

1. Product Manager- Julphar Bangladesh

- Formulate new promotional strategies for assigned portfolio as per the need of the market.
- Prepare and execute annual Marketing plan.
- Develop and implement promotional campaigns.
- Train up new recruited and existing Medical Promotion Officers.
- Produce different reports, briefs, speeches, presentations, Web sites and press releases.
- Develop yearly schedule and organize workshops, scientific seminars, conferences and other
- events.
- Act as spokesperson for the organization and answer written and oral inquiries.
- Prepare corporate brochures, reports, newsletters and other material.
- Monitor sales and achievements of assigned brands to take appropriate measure.

2. Senior Product Executive- Concord Pharmaceuticals Ltd.

- Devise new promotional strategies for assigned portfolio as per the need of the market.
- Develop and implement yearly marketing plan.
- · Develop and implement promotional campaigns.
- Gather, research and prepare communications material for Medical Promotion Officers and Doctors.
- Train up new recruited and existing Medical Promotion Officers.
- Prepare different reports, briefs, speeches, presentations, Web sites and press releases.
- Develop yearly schedule and organize workshops, scientific seminars, conferences and other
- · events.
- Prepare different types reports, newsletters and other material.
- Monitor sales and achievements of assigned brands to take appropriate measure.